

### CONTACT

- **(** 098-284-6992
- jaytanet@gmail.com
- https://transcendentconkies-d65958.netlify.app/
- 56 road rama2 alley 51 Subdistrict thakam District Bang Khun Thian Bangkok 10150

### **EDUCATION**

### **Business Computer**

Mittraphon Business Administration 2012-2016

### Information System

Rajamangala University of Technology Krungthep 2017-2020

### **SKILL**

- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind
- Antd
- Mui
- Bootstrap
- Louisiap
- Javascript
- Typescript
- JQuery
- React
- Nextis
- Redct

- Nodejs
- Express
- PHP
- MySQL
- SQL Server
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- Postgres
- AWS
- Thai Data Clound

### **TOOL**

- Postman
- GitHub
- Docker

# Tanet Limsumangkolkul

# Developer

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I am interested in working as a Full Stack Developer, with the ability to develop both frontend and backend systems. I also have experience deploying systems to the cloud using services such as AWS and Thai Data Cloud, ensuring that systems operate efficiently and reliably. Additionally, I possess strong teamwork, communication skills, and a commitment to learning new technologies to continuously improve system performance.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Full stack developer

(Nov 2024 - Present)

## Codemonday Co., Ltd.

Develop systems with responsibility as a front-end developer using the Next.js framework.

- Developed Hitachi's insurance claim system, including customer registration system and admin management system.
- Improve the efficiency of the Toyota Sure system by monitoring it through Google Lighthouse.
- Developed an E-learning system for online learning, Including the student system and the admin management system.

Backend Developer

(Sep 2023 - Oct 2024)

#### Rama 2 Medical Group

Get user requirements and designed the user interface, APIs, and backend for Anyhos system using Node.js and Express. Integrated Firebase notifications, payment systems, and external APIs (Krungthai Bank, Chiline, LINE Notify). Designed database structures using Firebase and MongoDB. Enhanced security with JWT tokens and encryption. Managed deployment on AWS, including ELB for the backend and S3 with Route 53 for the frontend. Developed admin management system such as patient management, payment and report.

### Programmer

(Mar 2022 - Nov 2022)

### Bizpotential Co., Ltd.

Developed system MRTA HR, TSRI HR, CRA\_ERP\_EDU, MUIC, and SIRIRAJ. Responsible for implementing new features such as email notification systems, Import excel data to system,

Generation transcript to Word format. welfare system, as well as submission and approval flows.